=My Little Perfection= (Adapted from the novel 'Difficult Pregnancy')
= حبيبتي الصغيرة = (مكيفة من 'الحمل الصعب' الجديد)
=Episode 11=
= الحلقة 11 =
Look at the time now.
انظري إلى الوقت الآن
Hurry up and come over here.
هيا أسرع
Mom.
أمي
You're being rude.
أنت فظ جدًا
The male host hasn't started eating yet, and you're already eating.
لم يبدأ المضيف تناول الأكل بعد، وأنت بدأت بالفعل
He's your host, not mine.
إنه مضيفة لك وليس لي
What are you saying?
ماذا تقولين؟
Stand up now!
قف الآن!
So what?
ماذا في ذلك؟
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
Why are you bossing around here?
لماذا تتعال هنا؟
Who am I?
من أنا؟
I'm the hostess of this house, do you understand?
أنا مضيفة هذا المنزل هل تفهمين؟
Mom.
أمي
- Mom! - Hostess?
- أمي! - المضيفة؟
Kneel!
اركع!
It's the modern era, why are you still making people kneel?
إنه العصر الحديث، لماذا ما زلت تجعل الناس يركع؟
When can the younger generation
متى يمكن للجيل الشاب
interfere in the elderly's affairs?
التدخل في شؤون المسنين؟
Child.
طفل
Since your parents didn't teach you,
بما أن والديك لم يعلمك
let me teach you.
دعني أعلمك
When visiting someone's home,
عند زيارة منزل شخص ما
it's unreasonable
من غير المعقول
to wake up later than the host
أن يستيقظ في وقت لاحق من المضيف
and shout around.
وتصرخ
Are you saying the elderly can't interfere in the young people's affairs?
هل تقصد أن المسنين لا يمكنهم التدخل في شؤون الشباب؟
Then your wanting to have a grandchild has nothing to do with us, right?
إذًا لا علاقة لرغبتك في الحصول على حفيد لنا، أليس كذلك؟
Of course,
بالطبع
especially for those with bad manners.
خاصة لأولئك ذوي الأخلاق السيئة
Let's sit.
دعنا نجلس
Mom, have a seat.
أمي اجلس
Sit.
اجلس
There's no need to be polite. We're not guests.
لا داعي أن نكون مهذبين نحن لسنا ضيوفا
We're here to collect a debt.
نحن هنا لتحصيل دين
There's no need for formalities.
لا داعي للشكليات
You...
أنت...
Lian.
بيان
Don't be too calculative.
لا تكن حسابيا جدا
They'll understand sooner or later.
سوف يفهمون عاجلا أم آجلا
Without rules, there's no order.
لا يوجد نظام
Not following the rules
عدم الامتثال للقواعد
will lead to losses.
سوف يؤدي إلى خسائر
Are what you said rules?
هل ما قلته يحكم؟
Aren't those outdated customs?
أليست هذه العادات البالية؟
That's awesome!
هذا رائع!
I'm so happy!
أنا سعيدة جدًا!
I've never seen him look so grim before.
لم أره أبدا يبدو كئيبا جدا من قبل
Mom.
أمي
With us here, you don't have to be afraid of him anymore.
هنا ليس عليك أن تخاف منه بعد الآن
Why be afraid?
لماذا تخشى؟
What's he going to do to you?
ماذا سيفعل بك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك
After all these years,
بعد كل هذه السنوات
I can finally breathe smoothly.
يمكنني التنفس أخيرا بسلاسة
Mom.
أمي
I just checked the yard.
تحققت للتو من الفناء
The corridor light bulb is loose, and there're wild cats in the yard.
مصابيح الضوء في الممر منسول، و
There's no ghost.
لا يوجد شبح
I think
أعتقد
all of this is done by Gu Dequan.
كل هذا يقوم به غو دهتشيوان
See, Mom?
أرأيت أمي؟
What did I say?
ماذا قلت؟
There are no ghosts in this world.
لا توجد أشباح في هذا العالم
You have to believe in science.
عليك أن تؤمن بالعلم
I believe in you.
أنا أؤمن بك
Whatever you say is right.
أيًا كان ما تقوله صحيح
Let's go.
لنذهب
They're really outrageous.
إنها فظيعة حقا
They dare to treat you like this.
إنهم يجرؤون على معاملتك بهذا الشكل
Chen Guihua is too foolish.
تشن غيهوا حمقاء جدا
She can't handle Yu Jing.
لا يمكنها التعامل مع يو جينغ
You do it.
قم بذلك
It doesn't matter whether she or Chunsheng's family have a kid first,
لا يهم ما إذا كان لديها أو عائلة تشونغنغ طفل أولا
as long as someone gives birth,
طالما أن أحدهم يولد
the family property will be yours.
ممتلكات الأسرة ستكون لك
All right, don't worry.
حسنًا، لا تقلق
I'll handle it.
سأتعامل معه
Here, drink this.
هيا، اشربي هذا
What's this?
ما هذا؟
This is a nourishing soup.
هذا هو الحساء المغذي
It nourishes your body.
إنه يغذي جسدك
No, thank you.
لا، شكرًا لك
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
You must drink it.
لا بد أنك تشربه
This was specially bought for you by your father.
اشتراها لك أبوك خصيصا
Let me tell you,
دعني أقول لك
my father would never force me to drink such strange things.
لن يجبرني والدي أبدا لشرب مثل هذه الأشياء الغريبة
If I want to have a child,
إذا أردت الحصول على طفل
it's my own choice.
إنه خياري الخاص
Even my own parents
حتى والداي
can't force me.
لا يمكن أن يجبرني
You...
أنت...
You're outrageous.
أنت فظيع
Who's the master?
من هو المعلم؟
Times have changed.
لقد تغير الوقت
It's best for you to care more about yourselves.
من الأفضل أن تكترثي أكثر لأنفسكم
The mindset of the previous generation can't restrict young people's freedom.
عقلية الجيل السابق لا يمكن أن تقيد حرية الشباب
Your ideas can't control us.
أفكارك لا يمكن أن تتحكم بنا
Let's go.
لنذهب
Why didn't you dodge just now?
لماذا لم تتفاديها الآن؟
You're next to me, why would I dodge?
أنت بجانبي، لم قد أتفاد؟
This way, it's cooler and more imposing.
بهذه الطريقة، إنها أجمل وأكثر رسوخًا
So you were using my care for you to show off.
لذلك كنت تستخدم رعايتي لتظهري
(Local cherry  40 yuan/kg)
(الكرز المحلي 40 يوان / كغ)
So many cherries.
الكثير من الكرز
How much is your cherry per catty?
كم هو الكرز الخاص بك لكل كائن؟
Are you the daughter-in-law of the Gu family?
هل أنت زوجة ابن عائلة غو؟
It's free for you, take as much as you want.
إنه مجاني بالنسبة لك، اقبلي بقدر ما تريدين
Why is it free for the Gu family's daughter-in-law?
لماذا مجانا لابن عائلة غو؟
Every year, the sales of our cherries are bad.
كل عام، مبيعات الكرز لدينا سيئة
All thanks to Mr. Gu who contacted buyers for us.
كل هذا بفضل السيد غو الذي اتصل بالمشترين لنا
He helped many of us.
لقد ساعد العديد منا
We couldn't thank him more.
لم نتمكن من شكره أكثر
How could we ask you for money?
كيف يمكننا أن نطلب منكم المال؟
Bad sales?
المبيعات السيئة؟
Gu.
غو
Calm down.
اهدأ
Your health is important.
صحتك مهمة
Take your medicine.
تناول الدواء الخاص بك
No!
لا
No one has ever dared
لم يجرؤ أحد على الإطلاق
to oppose me like this.
لمعارضتي هكذا
Go.
اذهب
Give Yu Jing a lesson.
إعطاء يو جينغ درسا
All right, I understand.
حسنًا، فهمت